

□ (+1) 647-708-5763 | Salimansour@gmail.com | Slimnsour.me | Imagin slimnsour

# Summary\_

Software Engineering student graduating from the University of Toronto in April 2020. Professional experience specializing in software design, testing, and implementation. Huge video game enthusiast, aiming to be a indispensable asset to a talented development team in the industry.

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

#### **Centre for Addiction and Mental Health**

**NEUROIMAGING RESEARCH ANALYST** 

May 2019 - August 2019

- Implemented imaging preprocessing pipelines for a diverse group of neuroscience researchers, efficiently preparing data for 6 unique studies totalling over 500 subjects.
- Redesigned large projects in the neuroscience community including dmriprep and Nipype, and created tractography pipeline tractify to decrease nerve tract image generation time for patients from an hour to 15 minutes.

#### Geosoft Inc.

**AUTOMATED TEST ENGINEER** 

January 2018 - August 2018

- Tested main product Oasis montaj through Ranorex by managing over 1000 tests for each release and reporting results, decreasing the average failure rate for each build by 30%.
- · Presented results in weekly meetings, communicating with coworkers in other departments to boost understanding of automated testing.

## Education

## **University of Toronto**

HBSc Specialist in Software Engineering, GPA 3.7/4.0

September 2016 - April 2020

- · Studied advanced subjects out of personal interest including Artificial Intelligence, Computer Graphics, and Machine Learning.
- · Achieved Dean's List every year for maintaining a high GPA, and a Scholars Entrance Award for being among the top students admitted.

# **Projects**

#### **Balloonatics**

GAME DEVELOPMENT

September 2019 - present

• Developing an action platformer, using physics, animation, and mathematical knowledge to solve programming challenges including seamless level looping, while also iteratively improving game feel and always keeping the user experience in mind.

#### **Ray Tracer**

COMPUTER GRAPHICS, UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO

September 2019 - December 2019

 Built a ray tracer in C, combining linear algebra, physics, and programming concepts to implement advanced features including multithreading, texture mapping, anti-aliasing, depth of field, and refraction to quickly produce photorealistic scenes.

#### Tractify

Neuroimaging, Centre for Addiction and Mental Health

May 2019 - August 2019

• Designed and built an efficient tractography generation pipeline using software design principles to greatly decrease runtime and provide increased functionality for complex problems, and containerized it using Docker for increased accessibility and reproducibility.

# Extracurricular Activity \_\_\_\_\_

#### **Game Dev Club**

EXECUTIVE January 2019 - present

• Coordinating with a team to gather resources and projects to showcase in biweekly meetings, explain the logic behind popular game mechanics to guide beginners, and engage in deep game design discussions.

### Skills

**Programming** C++, C, Python, C#, Java, R, HTML, SQL

**Testing** Ranorex, JUnit, Selenium **Game Development** Unity, GameMaker:Studio